Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
What did you tell Geyhatu about me
Gündüz?
Geyhatu is too scared to understand...
...what I’m telling these days, Balgay.
Speak up!
I didn't know anything about your
business here...
...neither your laws...
...until...
...your dog...
...brought me here and tide me up.
Allah!
You will tell me everything.
Know that I’ll cut you till your bones
are separated from your flesh.
Soldiers are ready, Balgay.
Any news from Longar?
No, Balgay.
He won’t return empty-handed.
Make him speak till I’m back from
Kulucahisar.
As you wish, Balgay.
Commander Laskaris.
Don’t return to castle unless you have
Sofia with you.
Do you understand?
Under the name of our Mother Mary...
I swear I will find
the Princess, Master Yannis.
Curse be on that day when the Mongols
and Turks came to our lands.
Master Yannis, Osman Bey is here.
Bring him.
Osman!
Sofia.
Where is my daughter!?
She showed me Selcan Hanim’s dagger...
...to prove she has captured her when
she came back from Tent.
I never forget, Yannis.
I got your Sofia.
What did you do to her?
She has comfort.
For now, she lays in her special cage like
a sheep.
Waiting his father to save her.
If you do anything to my daughter, I will-
I came here to make an agreement.
Only if you let me live...
...Sofia will survive.
What do you want from me? Osman!
Balgay.
Stop it!
Don’t resist.
You can’t treat me like this.
Open my eyes!
Leave me!
Open!
Bala Hatun.
It's our time now, Sofia.
Andreas, Salvador and Helen...
Where are they?
You don't need to know that.
I bring more important things.
You like him so much…
...my father.
Sheikh Edebali.
He is gathering up valiants and Ahis who
are willing to fight.
Osman Bey has very plans no mind
can understand.
You do not see the fire burning in
front of you and armies who...
...carry wood to that fire.
It’s a shame.
This hyena need a more powerful collar.
Untie her, Zulfikar Dervish.
Zulfikar Dervish!
Leave.
Leave!
It won't happen, Bala.
Whether I'm alive or not, your
end is certain.
You will vanish!
You better stop taunting and show what
you are capable of.
Now you see.
Little girl!
You slaughtered Ahi Evren.
Sheikhl Edebali.
Hakça.
Pehlivan.
Zulfikar.
Gonca...
Dervishes...
Ahis... All of them came. Sofia!
And Osman Bey!
Remember this day, Bala.
I never forget, Sofia. You remember!
Remember this moment.
Are you okay, Bala Hatun?
If I hand Balgay to you, Geyhatu will
raze this castle upon us.
Sooner or later, you know it is going to
happen to you.
I get along with Balgay.
Why should I betray him?
You are just playing games to each other.
Who do you think is going to win
at the end?
You?
Or Balgay?
One of you will try to kill the other once
there is an opportunity.
I’m the only one who can save you
and my Tent from Balgay.
And then?
Flood goes, sand stays. Yannis.
Then we will face you and your daughter
along with the demonic powers behind you.
Either you!
Or us!
Speak.
I’m listening.
Tomorrow…
You will convince Balgay to go to
İnegöl's governor.
He'll be convinced that he'll take the
castle and chests full of gold.
I know which route Balgay is
going to take...
...after his soldiers leave their camp
site.
And you will ambush them. Is that it?
Both of us will get rid Balgay.
Only with a bunch of Alps...
You don’t have chance against his
soldiers.
It’s my problem.
Let’s say you killed Balgay.
How can I be sure that you will free
my daughter once you are done.
I give you my word.
The son of Ertugrul Ghazi, Osman Bey.
Soldiers!
Being trustworthy and hostileness
are different topics.
I can trust you but sometimes...
...being trustworthy does not work like
that.
For our alliance...
...I present you the Laws of Genghis Khan.
You will hold it until I’m here
with your daughter..
What if you will be the one who dies?
Laws of Genghis Khan...
...are more important than Sofia for us.
You will give the laws and take
your daughter back when the time comes.
That’s it.
What if I sacrifice my daughter for
the laws and your life?
We both know how bad you want to make
Sofia the Princess of Constantinople.
Yannis.
You are nothing without Sofia.
What will happen now, my Bey?
May I come in, my Bey?
You shall come in.
Relax.
What happened to you?
We can’t be relaxed during times like
these, Efendi!
Something…
...something happened to Gunduz.
Tell us now.
My Bey.
We found two Alps of Gunduz Bey.
They are dead.
No traces from Gunduz Bey.
Who killed them?
We don’t know, my Bey.
Why did Gunduz leave the Tent?
Where was he going?
He left because he wanted to find
Osman and join him.
And now you are making
decisions about battles?
Do you think our war is different than
theirs?
Yes, it’s indeed different.
After Bey of Kayi chose to cooperate
with the Mongols.
Of course it’s different.
And it means our battle is different!
Then, why did you ran to my door and asked
for my help in times of need?
Why didn’t you ask for help from Osman?
Huh?
Osman is a fugitive.
You can’t find him if you look for him...
...and you can’t hold him even if you find
him.
So when you are in trouble you ask help
from a Bey you don’t obey.
Take a look at yourselves.
Remember well from which door
the followers of Osman Bey seek help.
Remember well.
Tell Alps to search the area.
What are you up to? My Bey.
Where are you going?
I need to see Balgay.
Gunduz went after Osman.
What can Balgay do?
Don’t drag him into this.
Mongols are everywhere, Hatun.
They may know something about them.
We shall go and find out.
Batur!
Come with me, my son.
Take good care of yourselves.
Osman Bey!
Brothers!
My Osman!
What have you been up to, my Osman?
Yannis accepted my proposal.
We will ambush Balgay.
Finally, the time has come.
He'll pay for what he has done.
What do you want to do, Osman Bey?
Taking Balgay?
No. Taking his life!
We'll show him how being
cruel ends awfully.
Balgay and his followers will see that...
... mighty trees grow in stormy lands.
If they try to cut our branches off, we'll
pull their roots out!
Praise be! Allahu Akbar!
- Allahu Akbar!
My Bey! Gündüz Bey!
What happened to my brother?
They kidnapped Gündüz Bey!
They are looking for him everywhere.
What are you saying, Erkut?
Balgay!
Balgay did this.
He wants to know who informed Geyhatu.
He'll see.
Come on valiants, come on!
We're going to Balgay's Tent.
My Bey! Shouldn't we wait for the night?
Balgay is going to the castle now.
He's probably keeping my brother in the base.
Now is the right time. Let's go!
Konur. You stay here.
It's just a scratch, my Bey.
Make this dog talk.
He's the one who killed Köni.
We must learn about Balgay's tricks.
The information we'll take to Geyhatu
will be his end.
Let's go.
Keep an eye on him.
I will, my Bey.
What tricks are you playing? Tell me.
Enough with that, Hatun.
You said you were sending clothes
to Batur...
... and they ambushed Bala.
Now Gündüz was attacked out of nowhere.
Tell me! Why?
Who is behind all of this?
- Enough!
- It's not enough!
If you're involved in these, I'll scratch
your eyes out, know that, Zöhre!
What are you implying, Hatun?
What I'm implying isn't important.
What's important is your concern
which you fail to hide.
What did you do to Sofia?
She looked like she had been through hell.
She deserved it.
Do you give everyone
what they deserve, Bala?
Give Osman Bey what he deserves, Bala.
Your love isn't from the vanishing kind.
I thought about it a lot, Gonca.
If I marry Osman while I'm in a situation
like this, that would be unfair to him.
It wouldn't, my Bala. It wouldn't.
It wouldn't be unfair if you talk to
Osman Bey about it.
I wouldn't marry him without
telling him, of course.
It's not about that.
Osman wouldn't give up even If I told him.
He wouldn't let his love go.
Then...
.. he'll want a child.
He will.
It's his right.
Then he'll either find another Hatun,
or he'll accept life without children.
What happens to us then, Gonca?
Talk, Gündüz!
What did you tell Geyhatu, Gündüz?
Did you tell Geyhatu that
Balgay had the laws?
So Balgay is...
... playing tricks on Geyhatu, huh?
If I were you I would talk
before Balgay comes.
Think about what he'll do to you.
Talk!
Cerkutay!
Take my life.
Or I will make you pay for this!
Remember that!
Take my life!
Your death won't be easy, Gündüz!
But I won't be the one who'll do it.
Balgay will be.
In agony, slowly!
Gündüz Bey! May Allah help you!
Bey! They tied Gündüz Bey up.
That dog Cerkutay is torturing him.
That dog who injured Bala is also here.
He thinks it was my brother
who informed Geyhatu.
And Gündüz Bey is not telling him
anything so the Tent is safe.
- You should watch the road.
- Okay, my Bey.
Listen closely.
There are guards all over the base.
Balgay's units are on patrol.
There are 80 soldiers in Söğüt.
Almost that many went to the castle.
There are too many soldiers in the base.
We'll suddenly be all over them.
Samsa Bey, your Alps will go in from
the East and the West.
Thank my Allah for keeping my blade sharp!
- Let's go then, valiants.
- Let's go.
I can't see the governors.
Where are they, Yannis?
They came. They said that they
will obey you and brought their gifts.
I said, where are they, Yannis?
I sent them all back.
Look at me, old man. Are you playing
tricks on Balgay?
Osman!
What about him?
He caught my daughter Sofia.
Where is Osman?
He was just here.
Osman came all the way to here...
... and you let him go?
Remember! He has my daughter and
your Queen!
What did he ask from you in
exchange for Sofia?
You.
He asked for your life in exchange
for my daughter's life.
What did you say?
"If I kill Balgay while he's in
my castle"...
... "Geyhatu would destroy our castle".
You're right.
What did Osman say?
"I will do it. You just bring him to me
and I'll give you your daughter."
Where will you take me and
give me to Osman?
I told him that you'll go to İnegöl's
governor and take his taxes.
He said he'll be setting up a trap
in the gate.
Good.
You will bring Osman back to me
so I can get my daughter, Balgay!
If my daughter dies, your dreams of
Constantinople dies with her, know that!
Osman!
They are Balgay's prisoners!
What did you do, brother?
Are you out of your mind, brother?
What are you doing here?
Brother!
Are you okay, brother?
I had hope until you came.
Now it's gone.
Sergeant Samsa.
Bamsı!
Osman!
I knew you would do something
insane for your brother but...
... I didn't expect this insane.
You can't even say the word bravery!
You're only brave towards women and
tied men!
Bala Hatun escaped from me.
But you won't be able to.
You'll die with your brother!
You came to Balgay's hell by yourself.
Hang them to the hooks.
They will stay there until
they are torn to shreds.
We'll have a feast when Balgay comes here!
- Balgay!
I'll give you such a feast...
... that you won't be able to get
enough of your own flesh!
Instead of kumys, I'll make you
drink your own blood!
Hang Osman first.
Freedom or death!
- Allahu Akbar!
Like a wall.
Good thing we came prepared.
Allahu Akbar!
Get them, valiants!
AllahuAkbar!
Hit them for the sake of Allah.
Don't let them!
AllahuAkbar!
Arrows.
Hit them!
Allah!
Osman.
He is more overbold than I expect,
Alisar Bey.
Till now, no one could break into the
headquarters of Balgay.
Yes he is, Melik.
He is such a overbold man that...
He is blinfolded enough to not see the
trouble approaching to him.
When Geyhatu hears what happened...
...he will dig Balgay's grave with
his own hands, my bey.
Till that beautiful day...
... I'll try to bury Osman and dündar.
We came here to carry soil to
the grave of our enemies.
Luckily...
Our enemies try to bury each other
before us.
Brother.
Stay strong, my brother.
Osman!
Ah!
Are you okay?
I'm fine, brother.
I'm fine.
Bamsi bey.
Protect my brother.
Melik.
Take out foods from bag.
We'll enjoy the view.
Let's watch the rumble.
My bey.
Braves...
...fight truly,Cerkutay
You do the dirty...
...when you see a brave man.
Let's see you.
Look at the taste of my sword
which killed a lot lof Kayı.
Come here!
Come to your death!
Come...
....to pay the cost of all the
young men you've killed.
That's for Balgay.
That's for my brother.
That's for all young men.
I'm not done with you, Cerkutay.
I'm not.
Hit them, guys!
We've crossed the snowy mountains.
We've become a strong lizard, Bamsi bey.
We attacked to headquarters, Samsa bey.
Well done.
Brother.
Osman.
There are important things.
We need to hurry.
Let's go before Balgay comes.
Erkut.
My bey.
Dundar bey and Batur bey are coming.
They have our horses with them.
Erkut.
Take Gunduz bey.
Osman.
Never...
...do this, my brother.
Go before Balgay comes, my brother.
There's something you don't know
Dundar Bey.
You are the only one who
gives the cure, my Allah.
Brother.
My brother.
Are you okay?
I don't feel anything because of
my heart's pain, brother.
All will be well, my brother.
All...
We'll come through it.
How couldn't I realize anything
till now?
How I've done these to you?
Goktug.
You shouldn't look at the
starting...
...but ending.
Look.
The result is good.
We've came together.
That's the important thing.
I wish....
I wish we had a father and a mother...
...and they saw us like this, brother.
They didn't , my brother.
They didn't allow us to live it.
They've destroyed our tents...
...father...
...mother.
But don't worry.
Everything will be allright.
How will that be, my brother?
How?
I've killed a lot of people.
I've been a cruel.
Will Osman bey forgive me?
Osman bey is merciful...
...as much as he is fair.
Wait a little bit.
We will wait till you are calm.
Then he will understand us surely...
...when we explain it.
Balgay.
Balgay won't stop following us.
I know him.
He won't accept it.
Even if Balgay tries to attack me...
..with all Mongols...
...I will not allow him to take you.
We've forgotten your wound
because of brother longing.
I'll bring some ointment for you.
I'll put it on your wound.
My brother...
Father
What happened here?
May Allah...
...protect us from what
I think, my son.
Osman...
How he could do this?
It seems that...
...the soldiers of Samsar...
...entered his service.
How long will itl continue, father?
We need to stop Osman.
Either we'll stop him...
...or the anger of the Balgay ...
will hit us.
Osman!
You were the same when you're young.
You used to speak a lot...
when you hurt yourself.
Mongol guy scared me a lot, my brother.
I hardly remember those days.
Goktug.
As we've came together...
...nothing will happen to you from now on.
Is it okey?
Yes, brother.
I won't get bored.
I will tell everything to you.
I will tell you our mother...
...father...
...our tent...
and even
our wars with tahtakilic.
I will teach all.
I won't leave you ever after the moment
I held your hand, my brother.
Thank you, my brother.
Thanks!
My brother.
You've done this eventually Osman, huh?
Now...
Who will save you from Balgay's hand?
Who will save you from me, Dündar Bey?
What happened?
Do you fear that your boss who
rules you will get angry?
Batur!
Stop, my son.
He signed his own death warrant.
You don't kill your brother.
If I don't take the revenge
of Suleyman Sah...
...from you...
...don't call me as the son of the
Ertugrul Gazi bey anymore.
Where is Gündüz?
I saved my brother from them.
What's it to you?
What they wanted from your brother?
They wanted their trouble and
got what they wanted.
Now, it's your turn.
Ah, Osman!
Ah!
What will I do with you?
You've done what you wanted.
You sold my father's throne
to Mongols.
Then you settled on it.
I've done it for our tent.
I've done it for you.
I've done it to save the life of...
...those brave people who followed you.
Don't you understand stil?
We don't want your favour, Dundar bey.
If you had killed us with your gun....
....you would be a little bit
precious for us.
But now, there is some words in front
of our eyes.
Victory....
...or death.
Our brave men have been killed
because of you.
When will you stop allowing
your brothers to be killed?
When?
They are martyr, martyr!
But the others like you
don't understand it.
They don't know, Dündar bey.
Samsa bey.
Bamsı bey.
What kind of a seigniory it is?
How we will pay the cost of
all dead Mongols?
We'll pay the cost with the
blood of our martyrs.
We will not allow such traitors
like you...
...to break into the homeland
that my father conquered.
Soldiers!
Kill all of them.
Don't force me!
Don't.
I told you don't force!
Don't!
Boran.
Follow Dundar bey.
Eyvallah, (okay) my Bey
It seems that he went this way.
Let's hurry.
Come on!
Alisar Bey!
You, huh?
I know you need help.
Come here.
Run, Melik.
Osman should follow you instead of Batur,
you can lose yourself near the river.
This is not Batur's trace.
This is someone else.
Who that might be?
Batur...
We don't have any
casualty, fortunately.
And Boran brother is after Dündar Bey.
I will have him one way
or another, Dumrul.
One way or another.
Come on.
Stop!
What is it, did my banner
lord fell from his horse?
Osman, Osman.
What about Osman?
Osman attacked your base.
He killed all of your soldiers.
And now he is after my son.
Let me go and track
him with your soldiers.
Do you listen to what you say?
You've heard it, let me go and
track my son with your soldiers!
Soldiers! Go after Osman!
Dündar bey will lead you to him, hurry!
Balgay, where is Gündüz?
Why did you kidnap my nephew?
What do you want from him?
He was the one who informed
Geyhatu about Genghis Khan's laws.
Betraying me ends with death, Dündar Bey.
Osman Bey!
Let's go!
Gündüz... My nephew...
I hope you are aware of your doings.
Keep your heads up.
I said keep your heads up.
Answer me, why would you
follow tyrants' words, why?
We were scared, my Bey.
Brave ones die once, but
cowards die every day, Şahin Bey!
Kayı's Beys are always strong.
Standing strong, honorable.
Now, know this well...
... and hear it.
We are inside the nest of those
tyrants that you sold Kayı's dignity to.
Do you think we are just
babbling and fighting for nothing?
This fight is a fight between right and
wrong, between oppressed and tyrant!
Traps that plan to
imprison Turks exploded!
I will make the world hear that
the Turks won't surrender!
I will swear on my black sword, I will take
the sky as my tent, and the sun as my banner!
My wrath will be doom for tyrants,
but hope for the oppressed!
Allahu Akbar!
My Osman, what will you do with them?
Let them go to the Tent, but if you come
to me again like this, I won't forgive you.
My Bey.
Balgay is coming here, they are crowded.
We've prepared such a greeting for him...
He'll see.
Come on.
What do you want from me, Alişar?
I rescued you from Osman,
isn't that enough?
You no longer reign over these lands.
And you no longer have
power on me, Alişar.
I have no power, huh?
Do you think your father
reigns over these lands?
Speak before knowing that your father
owes his banner lordship to your mother!
What did you say?
If your mother hadn't have sold her soul
to Balgay, your father would have nothing!
You are lying!
Your mother gave up Bala Hatun
to save you from Osman.
Then Gündüz Bey, to save your father.
She lied, saying that Gündüz Bey talked
to Geyhatu about Genghis Khan's laws.
- How do you know all this?
- I have big ears, don't you know?
I have eyes and ears everywhere,
haven't you learned by now?
Gündüz Bey was valiant enough to
sacrifice himself for his Tent's Bey.
He didn't say a word to
Balgay, he didn't snitch.
But your father, oh, your
miserable, coward father.
I came here as a friend.
What do you want from me, Alişar?
Where is Bala Hatun?
Tell me, and we are even.
Return to your Tent, and see
the truth for yourself.
I am asking you one last time.
Where is Bala Hatun?
I don't know where Bala Hatun is.
I don't owe you anything.
If you are a son of Bey.
Die like one.
Osman is an enemy of your
father because of you.
And now, Dündar will be an
enemy of Osman because of you.
They will fight each other.
Then, Geyhatu will deal with Balgay.
I will make all of my
enemies fight each other.
Wait until things are quiet.
Leave this dog's corpse
near the Tent by morning.
Let my banner lordship
bathe in brothers' blood.
Calm down, are you okay?
Water- Do you have water, brother?
Your brother would penetrate
mountains to get water to you.
You were like this when you were little,
when you want something, you would-
Idiot.
Erlik Han, send me your wrath
from the realm of spirits!
Erlik Han!
I said, "Let Osman come to me".
" Let Osman come, so this black
soil would taste his blood", I said!
" Let him come, so that this blue sky
would taste his dying breath", I said!
Erlik Han, either take my
life, or give me Osman!
Up.
While Osman attacking my Tent...
... what were you doing?
Cerkutay...
What were you doing Cerkutay?
They were crowded, Balgay.
Samsa's Alps joined with them.
Erlik Han, give me Osman.
Erlik Han!
Bala!
I was going to ask how you are, but
I no longer need to, as I saw Sofia.
Masha Allah (praise be), you are fine.
- I am fine, thank Lord.
- There's something that you're not telling.
Tell me.
I'd destroy the mountains for you.
I don't want anything else than
getting over these days.
- Gonca is waiting, I should help her.
- You are not telling me.
You are keeping away.
You ignore me.
This is not right, Bala.
Is it possible to ignore you?
Just let me be with myself for a while.
Inform Konya immediately.
I want new soldiers.
If they are fools like you, I will kill
them before Osman.
Did Söğüt's air poison you too, Kongar?
Samsa was in my hands...
Osman and his alps catched just in time,
Commander Balgay.
Shut up!
- You have failed!
- They were crowded, Commander Balgay.
We couldn't understand where they
came from.
Don't ever come with excuses again.
Never!
How did you escape, tell me.
You know, Commander Balgay.
There is no chain to hold me.
- Are they located?
- They took precautions.
They took Sofia and me to different
places. They use the whole forest.
It's impossible to find Osman.
Commander Balgay, Alişar has come.
Let him in the tribe.
Go and prepare.
We will take Osman's life tomorrow.
What's new, Konur?
What are you doing here?
Where is Kongar?
I am telling you, don't you hear me?
My Bey, Kongar escaped.
What do you mean?
Didn't I tell you to keep an eye on him?
Didn't I?
Water, my Bey.
He wanted water.
While I was pouring water into the bowl,
he hit my head in the back.
Didn't you tie him after we left?
- Didn't you?!
- I didn't, my Bey.
Get up!
You failed the mission, at least stand up
in front of me.
Kill me, my Bey, kill me.
Why didn't you tie Kongar?
Why didn't you take precautions?
I can't tell you, my Bey.
What can't you tell, Konur?
What is it?
What can't you tell, Konur?!
You'll make me kill my company.
- Get out of my sight!
- I won't!
I will not go anywhere.
I won't leave you even if you kill me!
Then why didn't you tie Kongar, ha?
Kongar is my lost brother Göktuğ.
What news did you bring me from Konya?
I couldn't go to Geyhatu.
However, I heard everything in the palace.
Talk.
Geyhatu knows Osman killed his
servant Köni. He went mad.
He turned the palace upside down.
They say, he couldn't stop and killed one
of Sultan's sons.
However, they say, if you don't take
care of Osman and take the laws...
Geyhatu will call you to account.
He sent a scout troop to find Osman.
They will arrive here as soon as possible.
Doesn't Geyhatu trust me?
There are many who think you took
Cengiz Han's laws for yourself, Balgay.
However, gossips keep coming.
- I don't know what he is thinking.
- Shut up!
Protect yourself from Geyhatu's anger,
Balgay.
I have come from a long way, if you
allow me...
I want to rest.
I have important things to do tomorrow.
When you return, I will have
new orders for you.
I heard that you gave the banner lordship
to Dündar Bey.
Until I am done with him.
Go.
Thank Lord, Allah gave you to us, brother.
- Gündüz
- Aunt.
Ayşe.
What are you doing here?
How did you come?
Osman brought me.
I couldn't wait you in the tribe.
Gündüz, what did they do to you?
Don't think about it.
My brother saved me.
From now on, we will take care of it.
May Allah give you the best, Osman.
May Allah give best to hatuns and
men who support us in this war, Aunt.
I would
never give my brother to those ignobles.
- Welcome, Hatun.
- Thank you.
- May Allah heal you, Gündüz Bey.
- Eyvallah (thank you)
Osman Bey.
Come with me.
I have something to tell you.
Don't worry.
I am fine.
Thank Lord.
I will say it directly, Osman Bey.
Our fellowship will continue on the war.
But don't expect me more.
I won't give up unless you tell me
the reason, Bala.
I was grown for these days. My mission
is to stand by my father.
I understand that love is not for me.
Why are you telling me this, Bala?
There is something else, there is
something else you are hiding.
This is all.
Look for another Hatun for yourself.
I am no good for you, Osman Bey.
I am under your command anytime.
May Allah ease your way.
Why is my father late, mother?
Don't panic, Aygül. Set the table.
Your father will come any time now.
- Father.
- My Bey.
What happened to you, my Bey?
Osman...
Osman raided Balgay's base.
He wanted to kill me and Batur.
He killed our Alps.
- Where is Batur, Dündar Bey?
- Osman is chasing Batur.
We searched in everywhere with soldiers.
But we couldn't find any traces.
My son...
My Osman went to get his brother,
obviously.
You're being a banner lord for the dog who
kidnapped Gündüz Bey and killed your Alps...
Then you accuse Osman!
Enough!
Get out of our tribe, Hatun, get out!
When did this tribe become your tribe,
Hatun?
Selcan Hatun, get out of here before
I do something wrong.
First Bala Hatun, now Gündüz.
There's a huge hole in your tribe, Dündar!
Do you think what you talk here
stays here?
What you talk goes to Balgay's ears!
Don't you understand?
What do you mean?
Say what you are going to say!
What I mean is obvious...
I came here to tell you that Ayşe Hatun
is not in her tent, but now I understand...
that my Osman took Ayşe Hatun to Gündüz.
What comes around goes around.
The day which we call you, not Osman,
to account for our Alps' blood is coming!
You don't have heart to hit me.
Hatun, Hatun get out of here.
Get out!
Get out.
The tribe and the tradition is ours.
Don't underestimate anyone, Dündar.
Everyone is on guard.
Saltug!
Prepare Alps immediately.
We will set off to search Batur Bey.
We won't come back before
killing Osman.
As you order, my Bey.
My Osman.
My Osman, come, come.
My Osman, what does bother you?
Does betrayal or the enemy bother you?
Neither betrayal nor the enemy bothers
me.
The fire is in my heart, Bamsı Bey.
In my heart.
My Osman, if you think of Sheik Edebalı's
willing, don't worry.
Edebalı is a mighty person.
He is waiting for the right time, my Osman.
No.
It is not Edebalı that bothers me.
It's Bala.
She said...
She said she doesn't want me.
First, her father despised me.
Now, the girl.
Now the girl despises me.
My Osman, why do you think like that?
Don't set your mind like that.
It is not my decision.
Bala decided that, Bamsı Bey.
She has a point, actually.
We are in a path that we don't
know what will happen tomorrow.
So, so, standing by my side has
crushed her.
It's been much.
Son, I know my daughter Bala.
I know my daughter Bala.
She is neither worried of tomorrow, nor
escapes from the difficulty.
Son, do not worry because of
some void reasons.
The heart carries love and the
patience carries the heart.
The love thing is complicated.
My Osman...
I think...
there's something wrong in this
and it will come out soon.
My Osman.
Waiting is the faith of lovers, Osman.
Be patient.
Be patient, son.
It's because of me.
Konur Alp...
what are you saying?
I'm saying...
I'm---
He's my brother.
What can I say, Sergeant Samsa?
You've done what's necessary.
I wouldn't forgive you if
you killed your brother.
It's brotherhood.
My brother Alabörü was
martyred in Mongol raid.
In front of my eyes...
I wish he was alive.
I would return him to self by
hitting with my own hands.
I wish he was breathing.
Alabörü is dead now.
I can only pray for him.
But you can do other things.
Protect your brother.
We're with you.
He doesn't believe me, Samsa Bey.
He doesn't believe me.
Konur...
Then why didn't he kill you?
He believes you.
Don't worry, Konur.
Göktuğ is the son of a brave mother
and father.
He has compassion in his heart.
As long as he has it...
it will be a hope for us.
Thank you, Sergeant Samsa.
Thank you.
Are the soldiers deployed?
They are deployed in the place you said.
What is our route?
Here. We'll climb over Kurtlar Hill.
In which route do the soldiers go?
From here. The other way is long and...
spook.
Then we...
will go to Kurtlar Hill.
How can you set a trap for me
with your lame brain, Osman?
You won't save yourself this time.
I told Yannis that I'd set a
trap in İnegöl border.
But the war is full of tricks.
We won't set the trap in there.
We'll set it in...
Kurtlar Hill.
Balgay's base is far from there.
They won't think that the trap is there.
They will be unprepared.
If Yannis told them where the trap is...
they may be prepared.
Mongol soldiers already passed Kurtlar
Hill and arrived at border.
We should've killed them.
They're useless, Bamsı Bey.
Balgay will use that way because they
passed that road safely.
Then they're waiting for
us in İnegöl border.
That's why we divide into two.
Samsa Bey, you and your Alps will go to...
İnegöl border.
They've
waited too much. When you go there...
kill them.
Bury their bodies in their caves.
Thank you.
Selcan Hatun.
You chased me out of the marquee..
and now out of the tent?
You'll help, Selcan Hatun.
I will help?
You must be prepared, Zöhre.
What can I do?
My Batur is still not here.
Osman meant it.
He'll kill him.
Tell him not to do anything mad.
- He'll listen to you.
- Enough!
You keep saying "Osman this, Osman that!"
Look at yourselves
before saying anything!
You don't ever see what mad Osman does.
What did he do? What did Osman do?
Tell me what you do first.
First Bala, then Gündüz, now Batur...
Get out!
Go tell someone else.
Tell Osman not to do anything mad, Hatun!
Osman should give up on his anger.
If something happens to my Batur, then
you'll see my real face.
Batur.
Batur!
What are you looking at?
Get him up. Take him to infirmary.
He's wounded, right?
Is he badly injured?
Where's his wound?
His mother will take care of him.
My Batur, my son.
Where's your wound?
- My Batur...
- Batur...
My son.
His mother will take care of him.
His mother.. Batur... My son...
My son... Open your eyes.
My son, open your eyes son.
Zöhre...
He's gone.
He's dead.
No!
No! No!
No! Batur!
Open your eyes, son!
Open your beautiful eyes!
Batur! My son!
My son.. My son!
Batur!
My son! My son!
My Batur! My Batur!
My son...
They killed my son, Dündar!
They killed my son...
Brother... Open your eyes!
Open your eyes.
They killed him. They
killed my son, Dündar!
They killed him!
Open your eyes, brother.
Batur...
Brother...
Open your eyes.
My son.
My Batur.
My son...
Open your eyes.
Open your eyes, son. Your father is here.
Open your eyes, my Batur.
Brother, open your eyes.
- Batur...
- What did you do?
What did you do?
Osman...
Osman did it to my son.
Osman did it.
Open your eyes, son.
Alps! Alps!
Everyone go out of the tent!
Search everywhere!
Osman...
You'll pay for it, Osman.
You will.
I'll call you to account.
I will for Allah's sake!
I will.
My Batur...
Come on! Don't stop!
Come on!
Brother...
Brother....
Beast!
Mother.
Get out, beast!
You killed my son.
Go to where Osman is.
Get out, beast!
Beast!
Osman!
Osman.
It may be a trap.
No one knows that we'll
come here, Commander Balgay.
They may know, Kongar.
As long as the sky and the
ground is fine...
holy trees won't fall.
Holy trees won't fall...
as long as they're not touched by
enemy's and bad spirits' hands.
Take it.
Balgay!
Osman!
What?
Are you confused?
You'll die and lay to...
- the ground.
- May your...
grave be bad!
You came to the tent
because of Mongol's anger...
and I came to you with the revenge of
innocent people you murdered!
My anger...
is bigger than my revenge.
Come to your death, Osman!
We're not afraid of the death...
we fight with our belief and
we chase death!
Allah-u Akbar! Allah- Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com